<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Superhero Facts</string>

    <!-- Strings for labels on app screen. -->
    <string name="did_you_know">Did You Know?</string>
    <string name="generate_fact">Generate Random Fact</string>

    <!-- An array of strings for superhero facts. -->
    <string-array name="superhero_details_array">
        <item>In traditional Spider-Man canon, Gwen Stacy is Peter Parker\'s girlfriend. However, she
            tragically died when taken captive by the Green Goblin. Her death made comics history as
            the first time a hero was failed to rescue his girl.\n\nBut in alternate universe Earth-65,
            Gwen Stacy transforms from tragic victim to hero, as she is the one to be bit by the
            radioactive spider in lieu of Peter Parker.\n\nSpider-Gwen was originally meant to be a
            one-off character introduced in Spider-Verse, an event that united Spider-Heroes across
            different dimensions. However, her character was so popular that she now has her own title:
            Radioactive Spider-Gwen.</item>
        <item>Doctor Strange first appeared in comics in 1963. Although born a sorcerer and destined
            to become the next Sorcerer Supreme, a childhood accident fueled a passion for medicine,
            and he earned his medical degree from Columbia University. Early success in his field
            lead him to be vain, egotistical, and callous - until an accident severed the nerve
            endings in his hands, rending him unable to perform surgeries.\n\nA search for a cure
            lead him to the far east, where he trained with the Ancient One in the ways of magic in
            an effort to stop the attacks of Mordo. Upon his return to the US, Doctor Strange became
            a mystical consultant. He spent time partnering with other superheroes on supernatural
            matters, including Spider-Man, the X-Men, and the Avengers.\n\nOh, and that awesome cape
            he wears? It\'s actually a mystical item called the Cloak of Levitation, imbuing the
            wearer with the power to levitate and fly.</item>
        <item>Iron Man was created by Stan Lee as a challenge to create a hero that no one should
            like and force people to like him. From the mouth of Stan himself:\n\n\"I think I gave myself
            a dare. It was the height of the Cold War. The readers, the young readers, if there was
            one thing they hated, it was war, it was the military....So I got a hero who represented
            that to the hundredth degree. He was a weapons manufacturer, he was providing weapons for
            the Army, he was rich, he was an industrialist....I thought it would be fun to take the
            kind of character that nobody would like, none of our readers would like, and shove him
            down their throats and make them like him....And he became very popular.\"</item>
        <item>There is a character in the Marvel Universe named Squirrel Girl, and no, it\'s not a
            joke. Her civilian name is Doreen Green, and her powers are derived from her mutation.
            Physically, she has a semi-prehensile tail, a retractable knuckle spike, and enlarged
            incisors. Squirrel Girl\'s also has enhanced strength, speed, and agility, and the power
            to communicate with squirrels.\n\nShe first appeared in 1992, single-handedly defeating
            Iron Man\'s nemesis, Doctor Doom by overwhelming him with an army of squirrel\'s under
            her control.\n\nSince then, Squirrel Girl has joined the Great Lakes X-Men and also
            helped S.H.I.E.L.D. and the New Avengers.</item>
        <item>Scarlet Witch made her first appearance in X-Men #4 in 1964 as a member of the
            Brotherhood of Evil Mutants. She was originally introduced as the twin sister of Quicksilver
            (Pietro Maximoff) and daughter of the mutant Magneto. However, in 2015 (perhaps due to
            Sony owning the movie rights to the X-Men and related \"mutants\") it was revealed that
            Magneto was not the twin\'s father, and they were not truly mutants: they were abducted,
            experimented on, and given powers by the High Evolutionary, and subsequently tricked into
            thinking Magneto was their father.\n\nThough regardless of origin, Scarlet Witch is a
            pretty amazing superhero. She has the ability to manipulate probability, causing
            disastrous effects on her opponents. She also has the ability to manipulate chaos magic
            and is an expert hand-to-hand combatant due to her experience as an Avenger.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
